thezebra.com 2019-09-05

# Privacy Policy | The Zebra

#### Privacy Policy (Revised April 2019)

Insurance Zebra, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Insurance Zebra", "The Zebra,", "TheZebra.com", "our," "us," or "we") respects your privacy. In that regard, we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the website www.thezebra.com (the "Website") and/or use our proprietary insurance estimate engine and/or other services offered via our Website (collectively, the "Service"), why we collect it, and how it is used.

In Plain English

We respect your good looks and your privacy! This document explains what happens to your information when you use our site.

#### Your Consent To This Privacy Policy

By using the Website or the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy and the collection and use of information contemplated hereby. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version.

We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on our Website or through the Service, and it is your responsibility to review this policy periodically. When we do change the policy, we will also revise the "Revised" date and may notify you or post a message on the Website and/or through the Service. Your continued use of the Website or the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

In Plain English

By using our site, you’re saying you agree to this policy and all it contains. The policy might change; we’ll post a revised version but it’s up to you to review the policy occasionally.

#### What Information Does The Zebra Collect?

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual or your account, including, but not limited to, first and last name, home or other physical address, email address and password, phone number, age information, social security number, tax identification number, policy and/or driving record information, credit information, and credit card or other payment information. We may ask you to provide Personal Information that will enable us to enhance your use of the Service, for purposes such as facilitating correspondence with you, registering your entitlement to access certain special features, or to complete transactions. It is always your choice whether or not to provide that Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Service.

Technical Information. We may collect and use technical data and related information—including but not limited to technical information about your device(s), system and application software, and peripherals—that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support, and other services to you (if any) related to the Service. We may also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, which could include your IP address, cookie information, browser information, and the page you request. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. If you wish to disable the storage of cookies on your device, you may do so using the settings on your browser or device. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our websites. For more information on deleting or controlling cookies, visit www.aboutcookies.org.

Location Based Information. You also acknowledge and agree that The Zebra may collect location-based data from you through the Service ("Location Based Information"). The Zebra owns this information.

In Plain English

We collect info that tells us about who you are and where you are, as well as technical data about how you’re accessing our site. We own the technical info.

#### How Does The Zebra Use Personal Information?

Except as otherwise set forth herein, or in any applicable Terms of Service, Personal Information and Location Based Information that you provide will be used to support your relationship with The Zebra and our products and services or partners. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information through our Service, leverage our tools in connection with your authorized use of our products and services, process payment, facilitate interaction with third party services, and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from The Zebra.

We also use information to perform data analyses (including market and consumer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal information), protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities, and comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.

The Zebra may use Location Based Information, as long as it is in a form that does not personally identify you, to improve, market or promote its products (including without limitation to comply with applicable laws or regulations related to insurance) or to provide services or technologies to you. The Zebra may also sell or license Location Based Information regarding its users to third parties, including Service Providers, but not in a manner in which the recipient will be able to identify you personally. You acknowledge that certain information or content that you provide in connection with the Service may inherently allow or help third parties to personally identify you.

In Plain English

We use your personal info to make The Zebra’s services better or more accurate. In some cases, your personal info will be shared with & used to help connect you with our partners.

#### Sharing Of Personal Information

The Zebra may share Personal Information or Location Based Information it collects about you to or with third parties, but only if we believe based upon your actions (including your actions and submissions via our Website) that the third party may have products or services that specifically interest you. Personal Information and Location Based Information collected from you is commonly used to provide you with products and services and to comply with any requirements of law.

Agents or contractors of The Zebra may have access to your Personal Information and Location Based Information on a need-to-know basis for the purpose of performing services on behalf of The Zebra. All such agents or contractors who have access to such information are asked to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing or as otherwise required by law.

We may also share certain Personal Information or Location Based Information with institutions providing possible product offerings to you based on the information you submit through the Website (e.g. financial institutions and/or insurance companies), and/or certain The Zebra vendors in order to allow them to use that information to obtain and provide us with additional information about you, and/or product offerings that might be of interest to you. In the case of insurance companies, Personal Information that is shared by us may be used by such insurance companies to “soft pull” your credit report. Note that any such reports would be pulled directly by the applicable insurance company and not by The Zebra.  A “soft pull” would not negatively impact your credit report, but once you choose to proceed with an insurance carrier, they may pull additional credit reports. The pulling of any such reports would be governed by the applicable insurance company’s own privacy policy, as addressed in the “Third-Party Websites, Services and Applications” section of this Privacy Policy.

The Zebra or its agents or contractors may disclose Personal Information or Location Based Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of The Zebra or its agents or contractors; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.

Finally, if The Zebra should ever merge with another organization, file for bankruptcy, or sell our assets, we may transfer the information you provide to us on through the Service to a third party or share your Personal Information to the company with which we enter into such transaction as a part of such transaction.

Notice To California Residents: Subject to certain limits under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents may ask us to provide them with (i) a list of certain categories of personal information that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and (ii) the identity of those third parties. To make this request, California residents may contact us as specified in the How to Contact Us section below.

In Plain English

Our agents might have access to your personal details in order to do their jobs: but they’ll do their best to keep it confidential. While it might be necessary to share your info to use our services, we take your personal information seriously and will not sell it indiscriminately. We can disclose personal details if the law tells us too, to protect ourselves, or in the interest of public or user safety. Some carriers may "soft pull" your credit when requesting initial quotes on The Zebra, but this alone does not negatively impact your credit. Finally, if our organization goes through a giant transition like bankruptcy or a merger, we might transfer your info.

#### Security of Your Information

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect Personal Information, and our systems are designed to protect Personal Information from unauthorized usage on shared computers in that users are required to log in through our applications.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Personal Information through public facing aspects of the Service, through e-mail, or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting Personal Information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any Personal Information you choose to submit in connection with these public features.

We may send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in the event of a security breach. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

In Plain English

We work hard to keep your info private. However, because the Internet can never be 100 percent secure, you give us your info at your own risk. When you put your personal info out there, it can be collected and used by others. We’re not responsible for keeping any of that information private or secure. If we have a security breach, we may email you (which could be required by law, depending on where you live).

#### Third-Party Websites, Services and Applications

Please be aware that other websites and services, including the websites of third parties that you connect with through our Website or Service, may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third-party websites, services or applications.

Additionally, certain Personal Information may be made available to third parties using our Application Programming Interface ("API"). Use of third party applications developed using our API are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third party developers. You should be aware that such third party applications may expose user information.

We may use third-party services such as Google Analytics to help us understand how users use the Service and improve the ways in which we interact with users, including the refinement of interest-based ads displayed to users. Such services, including Google Analytics, may collect information about your use of the Service through cookies, advertising identifiers and other technologies. The collection and use of data by such third parties, including Google Analytics, is subject to their privacy policies.

In Plain English

If you get to us through another site or choose to click-off to another site from ours, they might collect your personal info. We may also use services from other companies to help us understand how users interact with our services. Also, your info can be made available to third parties via software applications and other technologies. We’re not responsible for their privacy policies.

####  Remarketing and Retargeting

The Zebra uses third-party remarketing services (such as Google AdWords, AdRoll, & Facebook) to advertise on third-party websites to previous visitors of TheZebra.com or our properties. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement or posting on the Google search results page, Facebook, or various other websites within these networks or on the worldwide web. Third-party vendors use cookies, advertising identifiers and other technologies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the The Zebra’s properties. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and the privacy policies of these third-party remarketing services. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. AdRoll preferences or settings can be adjusted at [http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false). For general or other consumer opt-out, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics, which allows us to display ads to you based upon your activities within the Service using cookies and advertising identifiers on your device. You may opt out of certain Google Analytics Advertising Features by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

Our websites are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.

In Plain English

We often use tools for the purpose of remarketing to you on third-party websites. For example, if you visit TheZebra.com, you may begin to notice that The Zebra starts showing up in your Facebook news feed, or in other advertisements throughout the internet. Many of these tools offer you the ability to adjust your advertising preferences or to opt-out altogether.

#### International Transfers

Personal Information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which The Zebra or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

In Plain English

We’re worldwide, yo! And so is your info.

#### Access And Correction

To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may (i) have the right to access certain personal information we maintain about you, (ii) request that we update or correct inaccuracies in that information, (iii) object to our use of your personal information, and (iv) ask us to block or delete your personal information from our database. To exercise these rights, please contact us as indicated in the How To Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy. To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we may take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information. To the extent permitted by applicable law, a charge may apply before we provide you with a copy of any of your personal information that we maintain.

In Plain English

You may have the right to access and update your personal information.

#### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you, change your preferences or exercise other applicable data protection rights, please contact us by e-mail at support@thezebra.com or write to us at: 98 San Jacinto Blvd #2000, Austin, TX 78701
